ow
what are you doing i'm trying to flat
iron my hair but i keep catching my
scalp and it's annoying that's why i
hate flat ironing
are you burning your roots yeah i'm like
burning it oh good
grace tried this what is that it's the
i bought it the other day it's the
golden heart root iron and you can
actually get to your roots and your
scalp and straighten it without like
burning it because you know sometimes
it's
like oh yeah it's like the safer version
of a straightening cup right here
oh wow this does work still a thing
i got it right right on my scalp and i
didn't feel anything does it look
right oh it's a good way to straighten
my hair
all right guys i hope you like that
little sketch whatever you
we called it as a comedy review sketch
um so yeah we do have the golden hot
yeah golden hot uh root iron and um
like what we like about is that you can
get like right to your scalp that's yeah
that you can get right on your scalp
it's good but it's not
like a straight straightening comb like
one of them old school ones like it's
not gonna get your hair bone straight
however
the purpose for what i'm gonna use this
for is for when i start doing my hair
again and stuff and start
when i get to the flat iron part i won't
have to like get to the root of my flat
iron
yeah because i think with us when we
struggle when we do you know we do have
to flatter on our hair on occasion
is we don't get like close to the roots
so we're scared of our feet
yeah we're very kind of funny with heat
so because you know our grandma used to
burn our hair all the time with the
straightening comb but not our hair our
scalp and so um with the flat iron and
stuff we would skip
that part instead of closer to the edges
will be kind of like like still curly
and not straight
like the rest of the hair you can see in
the the clips that um they were at the
beginning
our edges aren't really that bad so i
mean if you have natural hair
um it might you know we don't have like
natural hair we have relaxed hair so our
edges aren't you know as coarse as
natural hair
so i'm not sure how this will fair with
natural hair um
but it does its job so um i do like it
and uh but the only thing i like another
thing i don't like about it is that it's
a little big i thought it'd be a lot
smaller um
so it's not really travel friendly i
mean you can travel with it but it's
definitely not
compact stuff for sure so yeah so
but it's cool yeah like i said in the
little sketch it's like the um
the safer version of a straightening
cone because the heat does not come from
the comb itself right here it comes from
the rod that's in the middle
so that's why it's a little bit safer
than that and then also
with this thing it also keeps in like
static and frizz i mean i guess with a
straightening comb you can do that too
but
this one is it lays the edges down but
it kind of keeps that frizz and
static you know sometimes after you
straighten your hair keeps it down that
base that's i thought that was really
cool about that
and it goes up to 450 degrees um starts
at 250 and goes
up to 450 degrees which is good so i
actually i am impressed with this thing
i actually really like it it's like
it's good if you want to like extend
your washers and stuff like that we had
a video where we talked about how we
extend
and stretch our washes and everything if
you want to stretch that blowout or wash
for like an extra
day or two or three days that's like
perfect and then maybe coming home from
the gym or something like that just kind
of get those edges if you've got some
sweat
going on kind of mess up the edges but
don't use this all the time you know
what we are with
yeah minimums a lot it's just you know
just keep it down to a minimum
but since i'm gonna start washing my
hair again i figured you know maybe i
should you know buy something that will
help me with
getting the roots and getting the edges
and everything straight so yeah i really
do like
it we are flat we are a fan so yeah we
hope you like this review and everything
um
if you want to see more like comedy
sketch product reviews let us know yeah
let's just
have fun doing this so fun way to show
how um we like products and every year
so yeah that's my new favorite toy and i
love it
all right y'all see you in the next
video bye